Welcome to this course on JavaScript Harmony.
欢迎学习这节关于 JavaScript Harmony（版本代号“和谐”）的课程
Oh, don't you mean ES6? It says right here.
嗨 你是说 ES6 吧 它这里是这样写的
Oh, right. Sorry. Thanks Richard.
哦对 抱歉 谢谢 Richard
Welcome to this course on ES6.
欢迎学习这节关于 ES6 的课程
Wait, wait. Sorry. It's changed again it's now ES2015.
等等 它又变了 现在是 ES2015
What? Again? Really? You know what, welcome to this course on the future of
什么？又变了？这样吧 欢迎来到这节关于 JavaScript 特征
JavaScript. I am James Parkes.
的课程 我是 James Parkes
And I am Richard Kalehoff.
我是 Richard Kalehoff
We will be your instructors for this course.
我们是这节课的讲师
Technically, Harmony ES6 and ES2015,
严格说来 Harmony、ES6 和 ES2015
they're all different names for virtually the same thing.
它们只是同一个事物的不同名称
The important thing is that these names represent
重要的是 这些名称代表
the biggest update to the JavaScript programming language today.
JavaScript 编程语言现今的最大更新
Fast forward from 1995 to today and JavaScript has
从 1995 年到今天 JavaScript 编程语言
undergone a renaissance of sorts by making some much needed improvements to the language.
经历了一些大刀阔斧的必要改进
And with these improvements come a whole new batch of keywords,
随着这些改进 产生了一批新的关键字
ways of writing functions,
编写函数的方法
asynchronous goodies and so much more.
异步简便方法等等
In this course, we will explore the additions to
在这节课中 我们将探索 JavaScript
the JavaScript programming language so you can write faster,
编程语言添加的新功能 使您可以更快速、
cleaner, and more efficient code.
简洁和高效地编写代码
In this first lesson, we will start by outlining
在此第一课中 我们首先将概述
changes and additions to the JavaScript Syntax.
JavaScript 语法的变化和添加
In lesson two, we will investigate updates to JavaScript Functions.
在第二课中 我们将讨论 JavaScript 函数的更新
In lesson three, we will cover new ES6 Built-ins.
在第三课中 我们将介绍新的 ES6 内置功能
And in lesson four, we will wrap things up by showing you how you can
在第四课中 我们将进行总结 展示如何
incorporate these latest updates into your next JavaScript project.
将这些最新更新整合到你的下一个 JavaScript 项目中
Richard, what shall we start with first?
Richard 我们以什么开头呢？
Well, a bunch of keywords have been added to the language.
添加到此编程语言的一堆关键字
So, let's start with one of those.
好的 我们先讲其中几个
Let us take a look at let in context.
看看 let 和 const 关键字
Yeah, that sounds good.
好主意